A Guide to the Papers of Homer Stille Cummings, ca.1850-1955
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES I: FAMILY PAPERS
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: investments in the Pickwick Land Company 1933 July-1945 March, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Pickwick Land Company Financial Statements 1942 June-1943 (Box 7)
  - Pickwick Land Company Financial Statements 1944 January-November (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Stille Cummings' house in Washington, DC, 2700 Tilden Street 1933 November-1941 October (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Fire damage at 2700 Tilden Street includes itemized list 1941 ca. August-December (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Income tax and a fire loss at 2700 Tilden Street 1941 August-1942 January (Box 8)
  - Personal Correspondence, Homer Stille Cummings to Captain James Dinkins, the "Little Confederate" 1934 July 13 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings mainly re: stock in the 700 West End Avenue Corporation 1937 July-1942 June (Box 8)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Federal Income Tax 1938-1944, 7 folders (Box 9)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Federal Income Tax 1945-1951, 7 folders (Box 10)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Federal Income Tax 1952-1954, 5 folders (Box 11)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Federal Income Tax 1955-1956, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Yale Law School Association 1939 February-1956 April (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: taxes on stocks 1939 April-1942 October (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Receipts fro Alston P. Coughlin 1939 April-May (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings with the Library of Congress, mainly re: the disposition of his papers 1939 September-1954 August (Box 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Florida 1939 October-1942, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: an income tax appeal concerning promissory notes of Shore Gardens, Inc. 1940 January-1942 August, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: E.I. DuPont De Nemours and Company 1940 November-1947 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Florida Hotels 1940 December-1942 June (Box 13)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Florida Hotels 1940 December-1942 June (Box 14)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Stille Cummings' house at 4308 Forest Lane, Washington, DC 1941 May-1943 June, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: First Stamford National Bank and Trust Company 1941 September-1956 January, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Eastman Kodak Company 1942 December-1946 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Travel and Resorts 1943 May-June (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Stille Cummings' insurance policy, Hartford Accident & Indemnity 1943, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: George Washington University 1944 January-1945 January, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Stille Cummings' house in Greenwich, CT 1944 February-1947 August (Box 15)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Akron, NY octagon house of his childhood 1944 February-1950 January (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Julia and Homer Cummings' health reports and the Lahey Clinic 1944 May-1950 December (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Stille Cummings' new automobile 1948 October 14-1949 May 12 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Christmas gifts 1948 December-1949 January (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: a loan to Shumway J. Bird 1949 April-1956 April (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: acknowledgments of Christmas gifts 1949 December-1950 January (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: with and re: Robert W. Fleming 1950Dec-1955 August, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: domestic servatns and social security ca. 1951-ca. 1956 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings with Frank Chapelle 1952 June-1955 March (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Matthew I. Fox & Company 1952 August-1956 July (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: stock in the American News Company 1952 December-1954 March (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Birthday greetings to Homer Stille Cummings 1953 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Hawthorne Roofing Comapny 1953 April-1954 October (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: history of Cummings Cement Company of Uriah Cummings 1953 June-1954 February (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: First National Bank of Palm Beach 1953 July-1956 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Connecticut Income tAx 1953 September (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Linden Lodge 1954 July-September (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Automobile Association of America 1954 July-1955 February (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: AT& T 1955 March (Box 17)
  - Christmas gift correspondence and gift list of Homer Stille Cummings 1955 December (Box 17)
  - Telegrams of sympathy re: Homer Stille Cummings' death 1956 September (Box 17)
  - Birthday cards of Homer Stille Cummings ca. 1956 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1933 May-1939 November, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1940 April-November, 1941 May-November, 1942 May-1945 May, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1945 September-1946 February, 1946 March-May, 1946 September-1947 February, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1947 February-1948 July, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1948 August-1950 March, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1950 March-December, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1951 March-December, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1952 April-1953 January, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1953 January-1954 January, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1954 March-December, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1955 April-1956 August, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Homer Cummings Golf Tournament 1942-1956 (Box 27)
  - Christmas card, Cecilia to [Homer] Cummings [ca. 1935?] (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous cards, including Christmas greetings 1936-1949 (Box 28)
  - Christmas cards of Mr. & Mrs. Homer S. Cummings 1948 (Box 28)
  - Chrimas cards of Mr. & mrs. Homer S. Cummings 1949 (Box 28)
  - Christmas cards of Mr. & Mrs. Homer Cummings 1950-1952, 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Christmas cards of Mr. & Mrs. Homer S. Cummings 1953-1954 (Box 30)
  - Christmas cards of Homer Stille Cummings ca. 1954 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, letters accompanying Christmas gifts & thank-you messages 1954-1955 (Box 30)
  - Family History of Homer Stille Cummings ca. 1900, TMs (Box 31)
  - Family record & genealogy re: Homer Stille Cummings' family n.d. (Box 31)
  - Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings re: the Cumin Clan, and Ruthven Castle n.d. (Box 31)
  - Entrance examination for Sheffield Scientific School of Yale College 1887 June (Box 31)
  - 2 ANS, Certificates of Homer Stille Cummings from the Heathcote School and from the Sheffield Scientific School 1887, 1888 (Box 31)
  - Examinations for the Sheffield Scientific School of Yale College and Yale Law School 1889-1893 (Box 31)
  - Thesis, "The Hydraulic Cement Industry of the United States" by Homer Stille Cummings 1891 May 23, TMsS (Box 31)
  - Class Poem by Homer Stille Cummings 1891 (Box 31)
  - Zoology Notebook of Homer Stille Cummings from lectures delivered by Professor A.E. Verrill 1891 (Box 31)
  - Oration prepared by Homer Stille Cummings in competition for the Townsend Prize 1893, AMs (Box 32)
  - Draft of an article re: Cummings Park in Stamford, CT ca. 1907, TMs (Box 32)
  - Medical reports of Homer Stille Cummings 1922 March-1955 February (Box 32)
  - Appraisal of paintings in possession of Homer Stille Cummings 1928 December 28 (Box 32)
  - "Frank Weston Passed...." (detective spoof); includes research material ca. 1928-ca. 1930, AMs, author unidentified (Box 32)
  - Legal Papers, "Homer Stille Cummings vs. Town of Stamford" 1930-1931 (Box 32)
  - Papers, pamphlets re: wine, including an inventory of wines in the cellar of Homer Stille Cummings ca. 1934, 1945, n.d. (Box 32)
  - "Fifty years later," a class poem by Homer Stille Cummings 1941 June, TMs (carbon) (Box 32)
  - Marriage license of Homer Stille Cummings & Julia M. Alter 1942 July 13, DS (Box 32)
  - Lists of books read by Homer Stille Cummings 1942-1956 (Box 32)
  - Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: Mezzotints ca. 1943, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings mainly re: stocks & bonds c. 1954 (Box 32)
  - List of limited editions owned by Homer Stille Cummings 1949 October 18 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous financial papers of Homer Stille Cummings mainly re: stocks 1955-1956 (Box 32)
  - Description of home of Mrs. Homer Cummings, Greenwich, CT n.d. (Box 32)
  - Address by Homer Stille Cummings on Edgar Allan Poe n.d. (Box 32)
  - Notebook of anniversaries & birthdays of Homer Stille Cummings' friends & family n.d. (Box 32)
  - Lists of names & addresses of friends and associates of Homer Stille Cummings n.d. (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous notes of Homer Stille Cummings n.d. (Box 32)
  - Notebooks (4) of quotations copied by Homer Stille Cummings, mainly re: literature & poetry [ca. 1890?] (Box 33)
  - Notebook of quotations copied by Homer Stille Cummings, mainly re: Socialism [ca. 1890?] (Box 33)
  - Diary of Homer Stille Cummings' philosophical reflections ca. 1907-ca. 1919 (Box 33)
  - Dieary of trip to South America 1921 (Box 33)
  - Diary of a trip to Europe 1923 (Box 33)
  - Diary of a trip to the West Indies 1930 February 22 (Box 33)
  - Notebook of quotations copied by Homer Stille Cummings, mainly jokes [ca. 1930?] (Box 33)
  - Notebook of quotations copied by Homer Stille Cummings, mainly re: inspirational literature n.d. (Box 33)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Audie S. Cummings, Homer Stille Cummings' mother 1921-1925 (Box 34)
  - Correspondence, condolences on the death of Audie S. Cummings, Homer Stille Cummings' mother 1924 August-September (Box 34)
  - Cards of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' childhood ca. 1905-1910 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: cemetery plot of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings, St. John's, Stamford, CT 1926-1932 (Box 35)
  - Note and miscellaneous papers of Cecilia Waterbury resulting from her trip to France ca. 1927 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and financial papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings, property in Sarasota, FL 1930-1938 (Box 35)
  - Papers of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings re: Income Tax 1933 October-1939 June (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: secretaries, maids, waiters, etc. for the Cummings 1933-1939 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings, mainly concerning stock 1936-1938 (Box 35)
  - Majorie Davies to Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1937 March 9, ALS (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and newspapers clippings re: Mrs. Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' European trip and presentation at Court 1937 March-July (Box 35)
  - Correspondence of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings re: personalized photographs (Box 35)
  - Correspondence re: a proposed book of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' memoirs 1939 January-February (Box 35)
  - Correspondence re: sympathy & flowers on the death of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings acknowledge 1939 July-August (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1939 September-1941 May (Box 36)
  - Correspondence re: Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' memorial service & Homer Stille Cummings' replies 1939 October-November (Box 36)
  - Correspondence re: the death of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings -- the mementoes to her friends 1939 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1939-1940 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings, the Beaux-Arts Apartment 1939-1940 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' income taxes 1939-1941 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings, Portland Electric Power Company (formerly Pacific NW Service Co.) 1939 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence and loose lead from "In Memoriam, Cecilia Cummings," including an index of names 1940 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Cecilia Waterbury Cummings Research Fund 1940-1951 (Box 37)
  - Legal Papers re: Cecilia Waterbury Cummings' Florida property 1926-1936 (Box 37)
  - Will (carbon) of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings and memoranda re: the will 1938 (Box 37)
  - Legal Papers re: the estate of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1939-1940 (Box 37)
  - DS, Certificate, Cours de Civilisation francaise a la Sorbonne of May Cecilia Waterbury (Cummings) and a photograph 1926 January (Box 37)
  - Reading lists of May Waterbury (Cummings), looseleaf from her notebook classes at the Metropolitan Museum of Art 1927-1928 (Box 37)
  - Notebook, May Waterbury (Cummings) notes on oil painting, sculpture, and Oriental Art from a class at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, NYC, Class by Dr. Kreil[ue] [1927-1928] (Box 37)
  - DS, Marriage Licenses of Homer Stille Cummings and Cecilia Waterbury 1928 September 1, 1929 April 2 (Box 38)
  - Marriage certificate of May Cecilia Waterbury and Homer Stille Cummings 1929 April 2 (Box 38)
  - Recipes of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings ca. 1933 (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous papers re: storage of furs and household purchases (Cecilia Waterbury Cummings) ca. 1938 (Box 38)
  - List of persons from whom messages of sympathy cards, flowers received re: death of Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1939 August 10 (Box 38)
  - 2 items, In Memorium for Cecilia Cummings (Box 38)
  - List of stocks and bonds of Cecilia Cummings [ca. 1939], Notebook (looseleaf) (Box 38)
  - "Tale of a Tie," a comic story by Cecilia Waterbury Cummings ca. 1939 (Box 38)
  - Biographical information on Cecilia Waterbury Cummings 1939 (Box 38)
  - Correspodence and Papers of Dickinson S. Cummings 1905-1932 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence re: Dickinson S. Cummings' accident and health 1934 January-October (Box 38)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Dickinson S. Cummings 1934-1953 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Homer Stille Cummings with his son, Dickinson S. Cummings and family 1940-1953, n.d., 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the death of Dickinson S. Cummings, son of Homer Stille Cummings and Helen Smith Cummings 1953 October (Box 39)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Homer Stille Cummings' divorce from Helen W. Smith Cummings 1907 February-1908 July (Box 40)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Helen W. Smith 1939 February, 1954-1956 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Julia M. Alter Cummings' Florida property 1936 July-ca. 1941 April (Box 40)
  - Correspndence: Congratulatory messages on the marriage of Homer and Julia Cummings, and thank-you notes (A-Z), 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Correspndence of Homer Stille Cummings with Julia M. Alter Cummings 1942 July-1954 October (Box 40)
  - Correspondence of Julia M. Alter Cummings with various friends 1943 January-1952 June (Box 41)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Julia M. Alter Cummings 1945 May-1956 August (Box 41)
  - Correspondence: Condolence letters re: the death of Julia M. Alter Cummings (A-W) 1955 February-March, 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the death of Julia M. Alter Cummings and contributions to the George Washington University Hospital 1955 February-April (Box 42)
  - Condolences and Papers re: the estate of Julia M. Alter Cummings, personal property, Palm Beach, Florida ca. 1955 March-1956 March (Box 42)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Julia M. Alter Cummings' house in Florida 1955 May (Box 42)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the estate of Julia M. Alter Cummings, mainly tax returns 1956 January-April (Box 42)
  - Invitations, calling cards, and mementoes saved by Julia M. Alter Cummings ca. 1942-1943 (Box 42)
  - Will (carbon) of Julia M. Alter Cummings 1945 May 31 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Papers of Julia M. Alter Cummings ca. 1945-ca. 1946 (Box 42)
  - "In Memoriam," Julia M. Alter Cummings 1955 February. 16 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: the divorce of Homer Stille Cummings and Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1909 December, 1928 June-September (Box 42)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings and Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1926 July-November (Box 43)
  - Correspondence re: Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1927 February-ca. 1928 June (Box 43)
  - Correspondence and Papers preliminary to divorce of Homer Stille Cummings and Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1928 February-ca. June (Box 43)
  - Correspondence and papers re: the Marguerite T. Owings Cummings Trust ca. 1954 June-1955 April (Box 43)
  - Wills of Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1920 February, 1926 November (Box 43)
  - Power of Attorney of Marguerite T. Owings Cummings 1927 March (Box 43)
  - Decree of Divorce, Marguerite T. Owings Cummings and Homer Stille Cummings 1928 August (Box 43)
- SERIES II: POLITICAL PAPERS TO 1933 1899-1933
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings with William Jennings Bryan 1898 February.8-[1916 ca. August] (Box 44)
  - General Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings as Mayor of STamford and as a member of the Democratic National Committee 1899 August 8-1906 November 18 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: the origin of his political differences with Alexander Troup 1900 January 9-1908 April 17, n.d. (Box 44)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, congratulatory messages upon his election as Mayor of Stamford 1900 April 2-17 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence and Papers of Homer Stille Cummings as Mayor of Stamford, mainly re: municipal gas and lighting 1901 January 13-1905 February 17 (Box 44)
  - General Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, includes correspondence as a member of the Democratic National Committee 1907 January 26-1912 October 12 (Box 45)
  - General Political Correspndence of Homer Stille Cummings, including Speaker's Bureau, Democratic National Committee 1913 September 20-1918 January 26, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Memorandum of Homer Stille Cummings' interview with Mr. Robins, Attorney for the New York, New Haven & Hartford R.R. Co. 1912 August 27 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, letter of resignation as State's Attorney, and Justice Wheeler's reply 1914 July 1, 26 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings with and about Chief Justice George W. Wheeler of the Supreme Court of Errors, Connecticut 1915 January 31-1931 September 30 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: the Democratic State Convention, mainly re: his address as chairman 1916 April 25-August 14 (Box 46)
  - Political correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, mainly as Vice-Chairman of the Democratic National Committee 1916 June 7-1918 January 30, 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, mainly as Vice-Chairman of the Democratic National Committee 1918 February 8-1920 September 2, 6 folders (Box 47)
  - Political correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, "letters from prominent men" 1916 August-1928, 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Political correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, "letters from prominent men" 1929-1932, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Correspondence re: Homer Stille Cummings' campaign for U.S. Senator 1916 October 14-November 17 (Box 49)
  - Political correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Connecticut Women Suffrage Association 1918 November 12-1920 August 3 (Box 49)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Lawyer's National Committee to Procure Adequate Compensation for the Federal Judiciary 1920 December 4-1927 March 15 (Box 50)
  - Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, including Democratic National Committee 1921 January 6-1921 November, 4 folders (Box 50)
  - Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings, including Democratic National Committee 1921 December-1922 January 11, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Correspondence of the Democratic Town and City Committee, mainly re: finances 1921 February-1928 January 28 (Box 51)
  - Checkbooks of the Democratic Town and City Committee, Stamford, Connecticut 1922 November 14-1928 January 28 (Box 51)
  - Statements of account of the Democratic Town and City Committee 1926 ca. August-1928 ca. January (Box 51)
  - Financial Papers of the Democratic Town and City Committee, the 1926 Campaign 1926 ca. September-October (Box 51)
  - Political Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings with J. Bruce Kremer 1921 February-1927 November 29 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence, reports and papers re: exportation of coal to Uruguay; resulting from Cummings' trip to South America during the summer, 1921 1921 ca. May 4-October 19, 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings re: Stamford Bar Association 1921 May 9-1924 May 27 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Cummings' trip to Europe, "Bankers' Tour" 1921 June 20-1923 July 28 (Box 52)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Cummints' trip to Europe, "Bankers' Tour" 1923 August 2-ca. December 31 (Box 53)
  - Typescripts fo Homer Stille Cummings' impressions of Europe resulting from a tour of Great Britain, France, Switzerland, Italy, Austria, Czechoslovakia and Germany, including notes 1923 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence, memoranda and papers re: exporting coal to Chile, resulting from Cummings' trip to South America during the summer, 1921 1921 July 23-ca. October 18 (Box 53)
  - Frederick B. Campbell to Homer Stille Cummings re: business meetings 1921 September 9-1972 February 24 (Box 53)
  - Correspondence of Homer Stille Cummings: letters acknowledging recepit of his Keynote Address at th Democratic (San Francisco) Convention, 28 June 1920 1921 September 28-November 3, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Correspondence re: the Kentucky State Bar Association 1923 December 4-1925 July 21 (Box 54)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings re: the Bar Association of Greenwich, Connectiut 1924 March 3-7 (Box 54)